The beat is back
StreetDance 2 is a music, romance, drama film directed by Max Giwa.
After suffering humiliation by the crew Invincible, street dancer Ash looks to
gather the best dancers from around the world for a rematch.
Ash, played by Falk Hentschel.
Eva, played by Sofia Boutella.
Eddie, played by George Sampson.
StreetDance 2 is a 2012 3D British dance drama film and
the sequel to StreetDance 3D (2010).
The film has been released in RealD 3D, XpanD 3D and Dolby 3D with
Max Giwa and Dania Pasquini returning to direct.
Britain's Got Talent stars George Sampson and Flawless return along with hip-hop dancer Sofia
Boutella (backing dancer for Madonna and face of Nike) and Falk Hentschel.
The cast also features b-boys such as Lilou, Niek and Yaman.
The film is a production of Vertigo Films in association with BBC Films.
The film explores themes of dancing, dancer, musical, street dance, salsa.
The tone is emotional.